<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Earthquakes around Me</string>
    <string name="load_more">Load more</string>
    <string name="about_options_fragment">Here you can modify different parameters of the displayed earthquakes. Like minimum magnitude or maximum magnitude of the earthquakes.
    \n\nPlease keep in mind the default values of the parameters and restrictions. Default values:\n
    - start date: current date and time minus 30 days\n
    - end date: current date and time\n
    - order by: time in descending order\n
    - radius: 500 km\n
    \nSo if you don\'t change anything, you\'ll see the last earthquakes that happened in the past
        30 days in a 500 km radius, ordered from the latest to the earliest.\n\n
        PS: Did you know that there are earthquakes with a negative magnitude? Set the maximum
        magnitude to zero and the radius to 20 000 and see what happens.</string>
    <string name="minimum_magnitude">Minimum magnitude</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="search_options">Search Options</string>
    <string name="no_results">We couldn\'t find any results.</string>
    <string name="maximum_magnitude">Maximum magnitude</string>
    <string name="order_by_">Order by</string>
    <string name="time_desc">time (descending)</string>
    <string name="time_asc">time (ascending)</string>
    <string name="mag_desc">magnitude (descending)</string>
    <string name="mag_asc">magnitude (ascending)</string>
    <string name="maximum_km">Maximum radius (in km)</string>
    <string name="number_between_zero_twenty_thousand">&lt;= 20 000</string>
    <string name="start_date">Start date</string>
    <string name="end_date">End date</string>
    <string name="date_format">YYYY-MM-DD</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="location_not_found">We couldn\'t find your location. Please check that the app has permission to acces your location and restart the app.</string>
    <string name="permission_denied">Permission denied. We need your location to show the earthquakes.</string>
    <string name="radius_incorrect">Radius should be between 0 and 20 000.</string>
    <string name="date_invalid">%s date invalid. Examples of correct dates: 2000–01–01, 2018–12–31.</string>
    <string name="end_date_after_start_date">End date should be after start date.</string>
    <string name="magnitude_details_fragment">Magnitude: %s</string>
    <string name="depth_details_fragment">Depth: %s</string>
    <string name="simple_date_format_overview">yyyy-MM-dd HH:mm:ss z</string>
    <string name="search_options_read_more">Read more</string>
    <string name="search_options_read_less">Read less</string>
    <string name="app_description">This app uses information provided by the United States
        Geological Survey (USGS). Which means that, unfortunately, you won\'t be able to see
    all the small earthquakes that happen around the world, each day. As a rule, only the
    stronger earthquakes that happen outside the USA will be shown in the app. Nonetheless,
    the USGS database also holds information regarding earthquakes that happened decades or
    centuries ago.
        \n\n
        To use the app, you must allow it to access your location. That\'s the whole point of it,
    right? To see the earthquakes that happen in a radius starting from the user\'s location.
    \n\n
        This app is not officially endorsed by USGS and the developer is not responsible for
    the accuracy of the data. Also, this app doesn\'t send alerts when an earthquake has
    happened. Nor does it predict them - which is impossible, by the way :).</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="detail_fragment_usgs_credit">Earthquake data compiled by the U.S. Geological
        Survey\nVisit the USGS at https://usgs.gov</string>

</resources>
